本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
哟呵  孩子们  我回来啦
Hey, everybody, I'm home.
买了礼物给你们哦
And I've got presents.
万岁  真赞
Yes! Awesome.
老爸回来啦
Hi, dad.
爸爸  我们好想你哦
Daddy, we missed you.
爱死你了  我的礼物
I love you, presents.
我是说  好爱爸爸
I mean dad!
好了  我在给一家叫做疯老锐的电器店做灭害工作
Okay, so I'm doing an extermination job over at Loony Larry's electronics.
他那边什么白蚁老鼠啊之类的真是四害猖獗
He was infested with termites, rats and great deals!
因为他是疯子嘛
Because he's loony!
好了  这个给P.J.
Okay, for P.J.
这个给Teddy.
For Teddy.
智能手机耶  赞
Smart phones, awesome!
太谢谢您了
Thank you so much.
那我的智能手机在哪儿呢
Where's my smart phone?
P.J正拿着呢  四年后可以传到你手里
P.J.'s holding it. You're gonna get it in about four years.
不过我给你带了个遥控直升飞机模型呢
But for you I got a remote-control helicopter!
真带劲
This is cool.
我们可以一起把它组装起来
That we put together ourselves.
那就算了
Ruined it.
怎么啦
What?
我觉得这是个可以父子同乐的好玩具啊
I thought this would be a fun father-son project.
那敢情好  你不如去找你老爸一起玩去吧
Okay, why don't you put it together with your father
到时候再找我好了
And give me a call.
其实我还给Charlie准备了一个好东西
And I even got a little something for Charlie.
我是快乐快乐的小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐 小马驹
happy happy happy horse
我是快乐快乐小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐小马驹
happy happy happy horse
我是快乐的小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse...
很快就会变无聊的
That's gonna get old.
我看已经让人受不了啦
I think it just did.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
■
翻译： Colonel C
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
发现鞋子被扔在了屋顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订  后期： WaitinZ
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第七集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E07  Butt Dialing Duncans
我爱死我的新手机啦
I love my new phone so much.
看  可以上网  看视频  播放音乐
See, it surfs the web, it takes video, plays music.
拥有它的陪伴  真是好幸福啊
We're just so happy together.
我从我爸那儿得到的最后的一份礼物是一本书
Man, the last present my dad got for me was a book...
书名是“学科学的乐趣” 猜得到不
Called "fun with science." and guess what?
那书名就是个大谎言
The title was a lie.
哦  你想不想来看看
Oh, hey, you want to check out
那部新的吸血鬼电影《黄昏》的预告片
The trailer for the new vampire movie "Dusk"?
哇  你知道我超爱那个
Oh, you know I do.
那些吸血鬼们好迷人啊
Those vampires are so cute.
那一定是不死之身产生的硬如岩石般的腹肌
There must be something about being undead that gives you rock-hard abs.
哦  听着  我们得去抢看第一场
Oh, hey, we should go to the first show.
时间是在
Which is...
呀  是星期四晚的午夜
Oh, Thursday at midnight.
我妈可不会让我在上学日里那么晚还出门
My mom would never let me out that late on a school night.
跟我学吧  告诉你妈妈她有多么酷
Just do what I do... tell your mom how cool she is.
之后你想干啥就能干啥了
Then you get whatever you want.
那真的有效吗
That really works?
你以为我是怎么把那件曲线毕露的皮裙穿在身上的
How do you think I got that leather skirt I can't sit down in?
不知道哎  我觉得自己不怎么会说谎话
I don't know. I mean, I'm not a very good liar.
你戴着那条围巾看起来棒极了
That scarf looks really great on you.
可不是吗
Doesn't it?
好吧  我一定能对付得来
Yeah, I could totally pull this off.
我希望咱俩被分为实验课拍档  伙计
I hope we end up being lab partners, dude.
我可不想
I don't.
你说这话是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
别逼着我说出来啊
Don't make me say it.
哦  太好了  我和Walter同组
Oh, yes, I got Walter!
真没天理
Oh, great.
你得到了科学俱乐部的主席
You get the president of the science club,
我却和这个蠢呆子Van Brundt绑在一块儿
And I'm stuck with this dumb Lug van Brundt.
你刚才说什么
What did you just say?
我是说
I said...
我很高兴和Van Brundt友好拥抱一下
I'd... I'd love to give a hug to Van Brundt.
不许过来
Don't!
遵命
Okay...
咱们是实验室搭档好兄弟啊
Lab partner buddy.
拿着我的电话号码
My phone number.
等你全部搞定了再打给我
Call me when it's done.
明白了  大块头
You got it, big guy.
不许叫我大块头
Don't call me big guy.
很抱歉
Very sorry.
嘿  好消息  我们是搭档
Hey, great news... we're partners.
是哦  我们不需要一起合作
Yeah, there's no need for us to get together.
我会自己独立完成并把咱们两个人的名字写在上面的
I'll do the project and put both of our names on it.
天哪  我爱死你了  老兄
Oh, I love you, man!
嘿  妈妈  您在做什么
Hey, whatcha doing, mom?
喔  就是检查一下调料  要把过期的扔掉
Oh, just going through the spices, tossing out the old ones.
哇  真酷
Oh, that is so cool.
这也算酷啊
It is?
也许只是因为是您做的方式  才显得特别酷
Well, maybe it's just the way you do it.
那确实  我排了一个体系
Well, I do have a system.
是按字母表排序的
It's alphabetical.
你看  香菜之后是小豆蔻  接着就是肉桂
Okay, cardamom comes before cinnamon which comes before coriander.
哇  我真想一整天都听你聊调料
Whoa, I could listen to you talk about spices all day.
-接下来就是小茴香  -好吧
-Then we go onto dill... - Okay.
接着一下子就跳到大茴香
Then it kind of jumps around to fennel.
但是我们不如来聊聊衣服吧
But instead, how about we talk about clothes?
比如您正穿着的那件光彩照人的上衣
Like that awesome new top you're wearing.
你喜欢这件吗  宝贝儿  我穿了好久了
You like this? Honey, I've had it forever.
我特别喜欢你肩上那块污渍的颜色呢
And I especially love that splash of color on your shoulder.
啥  哦那个啊
What, that?
我估计这是Charlie吐的口水
I think that's Charlie's puke.
我们聊聊你的鞋子好了
Let's talk about your shoes.
喂  哦  是Ivy啊
Hello? Oh, hey, Ivy.
你要我现在过去
You want me to come over?
不好意思哦  我想陪我妈聊天
Oh no, sorry. I'd rather hang out with my mom.
好的  下次再聊  再见
Okay, talk to you later. Bye.
你病了吗  是不是也要向我吐口水啊
Are you sick? Are you gonna puke on me too?
不是啦  为什么这么想
No, why?
你情愿陪我也不去见Ivy
You'd rather hang out with me than Ivy?
妈妈  肉桂能排在香菜前面吗
Mom, does cinnamon come before coriander?
这真是你对我说过的最贴心的话
That is the sweetest thing you have ever said to me.
真是妈妈的小棉袄
My little wooskie.
我是快乐快乐的小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐小马驹
happy happy happy horse
happy happy happy horse...
看来快乐小马驹需要换一下新电池了
Yeah, sounds like happy horse needs some new batteries.
别  这蠢歌一直在我脑子里挥之不去
No! I can't get that stupid song out of my head.
好了  好了  要不这样吧
All right, all right. You know what?
我们来装这个直升机
Let's build us a helicopter.
乐趣就从使用说明书开始
And the fun begins with the instruction manual.
老爸  真的非得这样子啊
Dad, do we have to?
是的  必须的  还有你知道不
Yes, we have to. Oh! You know what?
看来我们先得看这本“装前须知”的手册
We should start with the "before you begin" pamphlet.
哟  这儿还有个DVD呢  我们也要看一下
Oh, and there's a DVD! Which we will watch
就排在手册和说明书之后吧
After the pamphlet and the instruction manual.
老爸  这得花多久啊
Dad, how long is this gonna take?
哦  不会太长的  哟  快看这个
Oh, not long. Oh, hey, look at this!
哇喔  还有一张“在看DVD前”要注意的卡片
Oooh, a "before you watch the DVD" card.
还有什么事能比
If there's anything better
和我的BMF一起敷自制面膜更快乐吗
Than a homemade facial with my "bmf,"
我没听说过有更好的事了
I haven't heard of it.
-BMF是什么  -永远最棒的妈妈
- B.M.F.?  - Best mom forever.
哦糟糕  我应该笑的  可是我的脸膜会裂开
Oh my gosh! I would be smiling, but my face is going to crack.
你们干啥呢
What's going on?
就是俩闺蜜的独处时光啦
Oh, just a couple girlfriends hanging out.
啥  Ivy也在吗
What, is Ivy here?
才怪  我说的是我跟妈妈啦
No, I'm talking about me and mom.
我俩一整个下午都在一起度过
We've been hanging out all afternoon.
我们去了商场  去购物
We went to the mall. We went shopping.
还做了些不能告诉你的事
Then we did some other stuff I can't tell you about.
好吧  随便  我又没问
Yeah, well, I didn't ask.
很好  因为我们才不会告诉你呢
That's good 'cause we're not gonna tell you.
好的  我就去别的房间呆着吧
Yeah, I'm gonna be in the other room.
哦  老爸  其实我倒是要跟你讲件事
Oh, dad, I actually need to ask you guys about something.
这个礼拜四我和Ivy可以去看个午夜场电影吗
Is it okay if Ivy and I go to a midnight movie on Thursday?
星期四吗  那不行  第二天要上学的
Thursday? No way, it's a school night.
Bob  亲爱的  你是根本不明白吧
Bob, honey, you don't understand, okay?
这可不是部普通的电影  这可是《黄昏》啊
This isn't just any movie. This is "Dusk."
-那是啥玩意  -你火星来的啊
- What's that? - Hello!
那个有名的吸血鬼电影呀
The movie about the vampires.
《黎明》的前传
The prequel to "Dawn."
真逊
So lame!
好吧  随便了  你要想让她去就让她去呗
All right, you know what? You wanna let her go, let her go.
-太好了  谢谢您  爸爸  谢谢你  好闺蜜  -好Teddy
- Okay! Thank you, daddy. Thank you, girlfriend. - Teddy.
打给我哦
Call me!
你头发上是什么东西
What's that in your hair?
那是小发钻  学着点儿吧  老爷子
It's called glitter. Get with it, grandpa.
Emmett别烦了  谢谢你
Emmett! Thank you.
真不敢相信我得自己一个人做完整个化学实验项目
I can't believe I have to do this whole chemistry project by myself.
都怪这蠢蛋Van Brundt
Stupid Van Brundt!
喂  别叫他蠢蛋啊
Hey, don't call him stupid.
那是对所有蠢蛋的侮辱
That's an insult to stupid people everywhere.
那白痴甚至连数到十都不会
That idiot can't even count to 10,
赶巧这也正是他要一直呆在高中里的年数
Which, coincidentally, is the number of years he's going to be in high school.
看来我手机响了
Guess that's my phone.
呀  真古怪  看起来我好像是正在通话中
Oh, that's weird. It says I have a call in progress.
你可能正好坐在上面不小心按到谁的号码了
You probably sat on it and butt-dialed someone.
喂  没人说话啊
Hello? Nobody there.
一定是转到语音留言箱了
Must have gotten voicemail.
你拨给谁了
Who'd you dial?
是Van Brundt  天呐  是Van Brundt
Van Brundt. Van Brundt!
他肯定能听到我们刚才说他的所有坏话了
He's gonna hear everything we just said about him!
你是说是你自己说的所有坏话吧
You mean he's going to hear everything you just said about him.
咱俩都说了他坏话的  Emmett
We were both talking about him, Emmett.
别再提我的名字啦
Stop saying my name!
- 快把电话挂了  - 好的
- And hang up the phone!  - Yes!
- 好啊  - 好啊
- Hey! - Hey.
我那邪恶计划有效没  你有没有给你妈妈灌黄汤
So did my evil plan work? Did you butter up your mom?
我给她灌了一堆就像看午夜场里爆米花的黄油那么多
Like popcorn at a midnight movie!
那是什么声音
What was that?
只是我的电话响  它经常发出这种古怪的声音
Oh, it's just my phone. It's always making weird noises.
你是怎么办到的
So how'd you do it?
那还真是痛苦不堪
Oh, it was so painful.
我不得不浪费一整天陪她  还假装她有多酷
<i>I had to spend the whole day with her pretending she was cool.</i>
真是我这辈子最长的一天
<i>Longest day of my life.</i>
不过总算都值得啦
But it was all worth it
因为我们终于可以去看《黄昏》啦
Because we're going to see "Dusk"!
当太阳下山  他露出了尖牙
"When the sun goes down, his fangs come out."
脱去上衣秀出好身材
And his shirt comes off!
Teddy耍了个坏招骗我
It was all just a big trick so
就是为了得到允许去看吸血鬼电影
Teddy could get permission to see that vampire movie.
老公  她觉得我很土  就像我以前看我妈的眼光一样
Bob, she thinks I'm just as uncool as I thought my mom was.
真是土包子的恶性大循环
It's the great uncool circle of life.
好了  亲爱的  我觉得你很酷啊  但愿能让你好受些
Well, honey, if it helps, I think you're cool.
一点都没有好受
It doesn't.
好吧  那我们要怎么惩罚她
All right, so what's the punishment going to be?
禁止看电影  一周禁闭
No movie, grounded for a week?
罚的太轻了
Too easy.
老妈要发飙了
Mama's going to get even.
你知道不  每次你一说“老妈”
You know nothing good ever happens
肯定就没好事发生
When you start calling yourself "mama."
老妈我才不在乎呢
Mama doesn't care.
他在那儿
There he is.
我看我们只能硬着头皮进去面对了
Guess we should just go in there and get it over with.
老兄  我可讨厌打架了
Man, I hate getting beat up.
难道你以前打过架吗
You've been beat up before?
是没有  不过没吃过猪肉总看过猪跑
No, but I've heard bad things.
喂  Duncan  给我滚进来
Hey, duncan, get in here!
我们的课题你完成的怎么样了
How are you doing on our project?
还行吧
Okay.
你就只想说这个吗
That's all you wanted to talk about?
哦  不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
我很欣赏你的新发型
I love what you've done with your hair.
那啥  最近没听到什么有趣的电话留言吗
So... Heard any interesting phone messages lately?
没有  Jeter老师抓到我在上课时发短信  没收了我的手机
No, mrs. Jeter caught me texting in class and took my phone away.
-好险  -什么啊
- Ohh.  - What?!
这  这可真糟糕  是不是特别恨别人把你的手机拿走啊
That... that's terrible. Don't you hate it when people just take your phone
还把它放在  话说是放哪儿了来着
And put it... where exactly?
在她办公桌里  我放学后才能拿回来
It's in her desk. I'm getting it back at the end of the day.
闲聊结束了
I'm tired of talking!
- 我回来啦  - 回来啦
- Hey. - Hey.
今天怎么放学回家这么早
Aren't you home from school a little early?
我们不是等着放飞那直升机嘛
We've got a helicopter to fly.
我只翘了一堂体育课
And I'm only missing P.E.
其实还有语文和数学
And English and math.
让我们把这只鸟儿放飞天空吧
All right, let's get this bird in the air.
- 哇  - 你怎么做到的
- Whoa! - How'd you do that?
- 我也不知道啊  - 莫非是声控的
- I don't know. - Is it voice-activated?
试试  停下
Uh... Stop.
下降
Down!
- 别过来  - 哇呀
- No.  - Whoa!
你一定是哪里装错了
You must have put it together wrong.
不 不  那不可能  我每一步都按照说明书弄的
No no, that's impossible. I followed all the instructions.
- 遥控器在哪儿  - 天知道
- Where's the remote?  - I don't know!
天啊  爹啊  快做点什么
Oh, dad, do something!
我要  我看我只能赶紧跑了
I am... I'm making a run for it!
很好  四下无人  我们去吧
Okay, the coast is clear. Let's go.
跑进去拿了电话赶紧闪
Just get the phone and get out of here.
好了  我拿到了  咱们快走
Okay, I got it. Let's go.
哎呀老天
<i>Oh, jeez!</i>
- 给你拿着  -你发啥神经
- Here you go.  - What do you mean!?
我不知道该怎么办啊  快把它藏起来
I don't know what to do. Put it away.
- 你得改改你的态度  小子   - 知道了  老师
- That attitude better change, buddy.  - Yes, ma'am.
你俩小伙子在这干什么呢
What are you boys doing in here?
我们有个化学问题要提问
We had a chemistry question.
- 什么问题  - 呃  那个
- Which is?  - Ahem...
我们搞不清啊
We were wondering...
硼到底是由什么成分组成的
What's boron made of.
就是硼
Boron.
就跟你说过吧
Told ya!
好吧  我认错就是
Well, I stand corrected.
我现在可以拿回手机了吗
Can I have my phone now?
拿去吧
Here you go.
等一下  我自己的手机去哪了
Wait a minute... where's my phone?
George  我能借你的手机很快打个电话吗
George, can I make a quick call on your phone?
拜托啦
Please?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 哎呀呀  - 你有什么毛病啊
- Whoops. - What's wrong with you?
我猜我现在就是那个“硼”了
I guess I'm the "boron" now.
- 你欠我一个手机  - 很荣幸啊
- You owe me a phone!  - Gladly.
- 好了 P.J.  我们走吧  -等等
- Okay, P.J., let's go.  - Wait.
那不是我的手机在你裤子里响吗
Is that my phone ringing in your pants?
喂
Hello?
稍候  找你的
Hold on. It's for you.
不敢相信我们真的来了  像做梦一样
I can't believe we're here! This is like a dream.
一个我们和帅哥们调情的梦啊
A dream where we get to flirt with cute guys,
专门来看帅哥演的电影
Watch a movie about cute guys
邻座也都坐的是帅哥
While sitting next to cute guys.
午夜场《黄昏》的票已经售罄
The midnight showing of "Dusk" is sold out.
不是吧
Oh no.
- 怎么了  -快看
- What?  - Look!
- 好哇  闺蜜们  -嘿嘿
- Hey, girlfriend!  - Hey hey.
你们来这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
我来这做什么  当然是来找我的BFD一起玩啊
What am I doing? I'm hanging out with my "BFD,"
我最好的闺女小朋友  对吧
My best friend daughter. Right?
因为这不就是所有的酷妈妈会做的事嘛  对不对  Mary Lou
'cause that's what all the cool moms do, right, Mary Lou?
一整晚都在一起耶
All night long!
喔  Ivy  那个不就是你觉得特别帅的那个Randall小子么
Whoo, Ivy! Isn't that Randall, the boy you think is soooo cute?
- 妈  轻点轻点   - 嘿  Randall
- Mom, keep your voice down. - Hey, Randall,
我女儿Ivy在这边
<i>This is my daughter Ivy.</i>
她单身  而且热爱交往
She's single and loves to mingle.
Mary Lou
Mary Lou!
你真傻  Randall听不见你的啦
You're so cute. Randall can't hear you.
哟喂  父老乡亲们  我是Amy Duncan  Teddy的老妈
Hey, everybody! I'm Amy Duncan, Teddy duncan's mom.
而老娘就是Mary Lou Wentz  这是我女儿Ivy
And I'm Mary Lou Wentz and this is my daughter Ivy.
我们就是最酷妈咪  对吧  Teddy
We're the cool moms. Right, Teddy?
跳起来吧  Mary Lou
Hit it, Mary Lou.
- 惨不忍睹  - 还是别看的好
- I can't look. - Oh, good choice.
因为她们现在正跟接待小子在撞屁股呢
Because right now they're doing the Usher bump.
你整个回家路上都没说一个字
Okay, you did not say a word the entire ride home.
说出来吧
Out with it.
今晚你让我大大的丢脸了啊
You totally embarrassed me tonight.
答对了  这就是我的目的
Yeah, that was kind of the idea.
瞧我的道行
Look at me.
为啥啊  我哪里惹到你了
Why? What did I ever do to you?
你骗了我  Teddy  你从来不觉得我很酷
You played me, Teddy. You don't think I'm cool at all.
为什  你为什么要这么想
Why... why would you think that?
因为我听见你说啦
Because I heard you say it.
- 在你不小心用屁股给我拨号时  - 我
- When you butt-dialed me. - I...
哎呀
Oh!
就是“哎呀”啰
Yeah, "oh".
我不知该说什么好  妈妈
I don't know what to say, mom.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这才刚开头呢
That's a start.
我真的不该那么做的  我觉得很不好受
I should have never done that. I feel awful.
现在我觉得好多了
Now I'm feeling better.
好吧能不能帮我个忙  以后
Well, do me a favor. In the future
我要是再做什么傻事
When I do something stupid,
你能不能就像普通妈妈一样关我禁闭就好
Could you just ground me like a normal mom?
噢哟  Teddy
Oh, Teddy.
我想我们早就清楚了  我从来都不是个普通妈妈
I think we've established I'll never be a normal mom.
Van Brundt  嘿  你好吗
Van Brundt. Hey, what's up?
- 买了个新手机  - 哦  好的  我该付你多少钱
- Got a new phone. - Oh, right, how much do I owe you?
你们知不知道拿到新手机后是可以检查语音信箱的旧留言的
Do you know when you get a new phone you can check your old messages?
呃  那听上去可不是好事
Well, that doesn't sound right.
我听到你们说我的坏话了  全都听完了
I heard what you said about me. All of it!
得  你准备拿我们怎么办
Okay, what are you going to do to us?
我让你们自己选
I'm going to let you choose.
- 给你们列了张单子  -哇塞
- I made a list. - Wow.
你对当恶霸还真有一套学问啊
You're pretty organized for a bully.
我不是有意要纠正你  不过gouge(挖)这个词里没有J字母
I don't mean to correct you, but there's no "j" in gouge.
我们就要第五个吧  至少这个不会痛
Let's go with number five. At least it's not painful.
- 来两份五号套餐  - 谢谢
- Two number fives, please. - Thank you.
我们错拨了Van Brundt的号码
We butt-dialed van Brundt.
我没说停下
I didn't say stop.
好啦  直升机  现在是你的告别演出
Okay, whirlybird, this is your final mission.
把快乐小马驹拖得越远越好
Take happy happy horse far far away.
发动准备  三  二  一
Launch... three, two, one.
干的不错
<i>Yeah, it's going good.</i>
别 别  不要啊  直升机
No no. No, whirlybird.
小心电线  不要啊
Look out for the power line, no!
我是快乐快乐小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐小马驹
happy happy happy horse
我是快乐 快乐小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐小马驹
happy happy happy horse
我是快乐 快乐小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse...
快乐 快乐 快乐小马驹
happy happy happy horse
我是快乐 快乐小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐的小马驹
happy happy happy horse.
嘿  小Charlie  那今天呢
Hey, Charlie, so...
我有个小小的忠告要告诉你
I have a little advice for you.
如果你以后想愚弄父母的话
If you ever want to fool a parent,
想让他们认为自己很酷  最好是找老爸去骗
And make them think they're cool, dad is definitely the way to go.
只要问问他的工作假装你很感兴趣就好
Just ask him about his job and pretend you're interested.
我听见了  你被关禁闭了
<i>Heard that. You're grounded.</i>
天啊  宝宝监控器在这儿
Baby monitor!
天杀的傻科技
Stupid technology.
还是听得见哦
<i>Heard that too.</i>
是哦  我真不能想象
Yeah, I can't even imagine
当你长大到少年时  人家还能发明出什么小玩意儿来  所以呢
What kind of gadgets they'll have when you're a teenager, so...
祝你好运啰  Charlie
<i>Good luck, Charlie.</i>
嘿  宝贝儿  给你  小心烫
Hey, honey. Here we go. Careful it's hot.
我有个小问题要问你
I had a little quick question to ask you.
当然可以了  妈妈  什么事啊
Sure, mom, what's up?
好吧  我要你老实告诉我
Okay, I want you just to be totally honest with me.
我是不是比Ivy她妈要酷啊
I am cooler than Mary Lou Wentz, right?
当然啦  妈妈
Of course you are, mom.
好了  现在告诉我实话  我是不是比Amy Duncan更酷啊
Now tell me the truth. I am cooler than Amy Duncan, right?
绝对的
Definitely.
嘿  甜心
<i>Hey, sweetheart.</i>
是的  我正在跟你说话呢
<i>Yeah, I'm talking to you.</i>
听着  你那哥哥是个麻烦
<i>Listen, we got a problem with your brother.</i>
不是这个  是你的小哥哥
<i>Not him, the little one</i>
有张大嘴巴的那个
<i>with the big mouth.</i>
- 你在跟小Charlie说话吗  - 啥
- You just talking with Charlie? - What?
没事了
Never mind.
话说那臭小子竟然打算把我扔了
<i>Anyway, that little stinker was trying to get rid of me.</i>
我说咱们先把他解决了再说
<i>I say we get rid of him.</i>
因为那样做才会使我变成
<i>'cause that would make me...</i>
快乐 快乐小马驹
a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐小马驹
happy happy happy horse.
这笨马
Stupid horse.
给我小心点  小子
<i>Watch your back, kid.</i>
我是快乐 快乐小马驹
I'm a happy happy horse
快乐 快乐 快乐小马驹
happy happy happy horse.